Emeka Onyedika

MERN stack and Solidity Programmer.

Location: Nigeria

Email: chuksremi15@gmail.com Phone: +2348160564759

Github: https://github.com/chuksremi15 Portfolio: https://chuksremyblog.web.app/ Linkedin: click to redirect to linkedin

Full-stack and blockchain programmer with over 5 years of experience. Solid skills in HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Redux, Node.js, Solidity. Experienced project team lead. Willing to learn and improve along with conventions in the ecosystem. Graduate of Computer Science.

Technical Skills

Node.js React Solidity Typescript Redux MongoDB Next.js

Additional skills:

Ethers Firebase Blockchain Hardhat Truffle Docker

Express.js

TailwindCss MongoDB

Work History

September 2024 - Present | 7 months

Blockchain programmer at Clynto | USA

clynto.com

Clynto is an on-chain lending and borrowing protocol that allows users to

lend and borrow crypto assets on EVM compatible blockchain using a peer-to-peer model • Developed and deployed a proxy-based smart contract to implement

- Clynto's lending and borrowing model. Wrote comprehensive unit tests for the smart contract, hooks, and end-to-
- end (E2E) workflows Utilized Solidity, TypeScript, Hardhat, Viem, Wagmi, React Query, and
- Playwright for development and testing.

Blockchain programmer at BuidlGuidl USA

BuidlGuidl porfolio

October 2023 - May 2024 | 8 months

BuidlGuidl is a decentralized autonomous organization acting as the community and incentivization layer around scaffold-eth and

speedrunethereum.com • Built and shipped buildlguidl challenge problems and personal blockchain projects.

- Utilized Solidity, Typescript, Hardhat, Viem, Wagmi, React-query.

https://aimovement.tech/

MERN stack dev at Al Movement | Nigeria

Al Movement is a community of private investors, institutional investors,

September 2022 - December 2023 | 1 year 4 months

small team of one frontend programmer and a UI/UX person.

 Responsible for the full cycles of the application development which include writing code, writing tests, and inspecting all code base.

and technology experts. I worked as the CTO at Al Movement, with a

- Drawing out system architecture/blueprints for projects. Ensuring smooth functionality of our app and fixing bugs
- Worked with React, Express.js, Redux.
- Full-stack Blockchain Programmer at Omitch | Nigeria January 2022 - June 2022 | 6 months Webapp: https://omitchapp.web.app/

Omitch is a casino start-up that integrated web2 games and handle payments with web3 Responsible for the full cycles of the blockchain development which include

Website: https://omitchgames.web.app/

 Converted casino business logic to code. Integrated games from a gaming provider

writing smart contracts, writing tests, and integrating ABIs to frontend.

This project didn't take off due to the teams inability to raise fund as a consequence the game providers have disconnected access.

• Worked with Hardhat, Mocha, Chai, Ethers, and Web3js.

Canary tech is the parent company of parapay, a fintech startup. Collaborated with a team of two developers in building the admin section of the

Frontend Programmer at Canary Tech | Nigeria

December 2020 - December 2021 | 1 year

- Integrated API's to frontend Applications. • Worked with Chakra UI, Sass, Redux-saga.
- The product has handled more than 1 billion naira in transactions

Developed Admin front end using react and redux-saga for state management

ENSinapp

ENScheap https://enscheap.vercel.app

Projects

fintech app.

A contract that allows you own a 3LD ens name by paying a fee to the contract. This is made possible by the ENS Name wrapper.

https://ensinapp.vercel.app

of ens name in-app.

Carbon ENS wallet https://carbonenswallet.web.app

Blockchain wallet built that assigns ens subname to users during onboarding.

Interfaces, Wagmi and react-query wrapper of the library ens.js for the registration

Chain link CLI(NPM package) https://www.npmjs.com/package/chainpeekcli

line and for deploying single file smart contract.

Color city NFT https://colorcity.vercel.app

ERC-721 token. Individual NFTs are dynamic image of the city of Toronto, Canada.

Blockchain CLI that gives you easy access to blockchain data from your command

Multisig smart contract

https://supermultisigwallet.surge.sh

This smart contract acts as an off-chain signature-based shared wallet amongst different signers hence the name multi-signature(multi-sig)

Education

Nnamdi Azikiwe University

December 2017 - December 2021